

ABOUT ME

Hi there! I am Emmanuel! You might also know me as Rapoo. I've been coding for over 4 years now. As a Full Stack developer. good with React-Js, Typescript, Laravel and MySql. I've worked with startups and large corporations to help build & scale their companies. Along the journey I realised my passion existed in helping others excel and pursue their dreams as upcoming developers and most especially love building new ideas on different projects.

With this passion, I have now built many projects and still working on building much more projects. I deliver REAL VALUE by teaching REAL WORLD projects to help students enter the world of web development. You'll get hands-on experience and learn the skills that are required to succeed in the real-world and enjoy wonderful sites and applications built and delivered right on Time

LINKS

MY PORTFOLIO:

https://aniemmanuelrapoo.netlify.a

ANI EMMANUEL SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/INSTRUCTOR

33 NIKE ROAD ABAKPA NIKE, Abakpa, 400103, Nigeria

08183225008

aniemmanuelrapo@gail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

MORDEN IDEAL COLLEGE

ENUGU May 2020 - Jul 2021

WEB TUTOR

I TEACH WEB DEVELOPMENT AND FRONT END DESIGN LIKE HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, TAILWIND CSS, BOOTSTRAP AND MANY OTHERS

DIGITAL DREAMS ACADEMY

ENUGU Aug 2021 - Feb 2022

WEB TUTOR AND FRONT END DEVELOPER

I TEACH WEB DEVELOPMENT, REACT JS, REDUX, JAVASCRIPT, NODE JS, MONGO DB, TAILWIND CSS, STYLED COMPONENT, TWIN, EXPRESS JS, REST API, REACT BOOTSTRAP, FIREBASE AND MANY OTHERS.

ALSO WORK AS A FRONT END DEVELOPER

GRADENET ICT

JALINGO Feb 2022 - Present

WEB TUTOR AND FULL STACK DEVELOPER

This Is My Place Of Primary Assignment For My National Youth Service Corps (NYSC) I Thought Web Development, Also Work As A Full Stack Developer With React js As Frontend And Laravel and MySql As Backend

EDUCATION

TANSIAN UNIVERSITY ANABRA STATE

ANABRA STATI

Bachelor of Technology

STARTED FROM 2017 TO 2021, WAS WORKING AND GOING TO SCHOOL AS WELL

MODERN IDEAL COLLEGE Enugu State 2016

West African Senior School Certificate Examination (WASSCE)

SKILLS

REACT JS	JAVASRIPT
NODE JS	EXPRESS JS
REDUX	WEB DEVELOPMENT
MYSQL	LARAVEL
REST API	